

CHANSE SHIRLEY

ABOUT

A versatile and highly organized young professional possessing 7+ years of experience in multiple fields, with 2+ years of leadership and event planning experience. Seeking opportunity to contribute my communicative strengths, analytical acumen, and diverse interpersonal skillset as Operations Specialist for Keyence.

EDUCATION

University of Minnesota
May 2015
Bachelor of Arts,
English Language and Literature
Minor in Sociology
cum laude

LEADERSHIP

WELCOME WEEK EVENT STAFF CAPTAIN • UMN • 2014

ORIENTATION LEADER • UMN• 2013

EXPERIENCE

SHOE PHOTOGRAPHER • LEX GET IT • 2022

- Streamlined each and every step of my photography process to maximize efficiency, doubling my output from 7 to 14 shoes/hour within just one month.
- Having developed an impeccable attention to detail, I now produce 3,000 to 4,000 photos a week with zero mistakes or flaws.

SERVER • MOTO-I SAKE AND RAMEN HOUSE • 2018 - 2020

- Excelled in fostering rapport with patrons through my interpersonal strengths, providing knowledge and reassurance while cultivating an outstanding dining experience, the proof of which is best illustrated by the increase in nightly sales of over 12% over the course of my employ.
- Harnessing my ability to multi-task efficiently in a fast-paced, highpressure environment, I ascended from my original position of host to server asst. within months and was promoted to server within a year.

ENGLISH TEACHER • WAT METHANG KARAWAS SCHOOL • 2015 - 2016

- Proving my organizational acumen, I independently devised a curriculum which I carried out to great effect—as evidenced by the 20% increase in test scores from my students over the course of the year.
- In moving to rural Thailand, I challenged myself to embrace adversity and to adapt in real time to a totally different environment. The crosscultural connections I discovered taught me the immense growth potential of radically new experiences.

STUDENT ENGAGEMENT INTERN • UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA • 2013 - 2014

- Carried out a comprehensive multi-media campaign, including pop-up events and video production, to drive enthusiasm for performances and promote the grand reopening of Northrop Auditorium.
- Managed email and calendar invites, cultivating relationships with different student groups and collaborating on events to generate energy for the performance arts.



